<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>inactive_class on Jeds Digital Home</title>
    <link>/website_copy/tags/inactive_class/</link>
    <description>Recent content in inactive_class on Jeds Digital Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/website_copy/tags/inactive_class/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Applied Statistics</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/ids138/ids138/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/ids138/ids138/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to IDS 138: Intro to Applied Statistics! This is my personal website, which I will update in lieu of the WISE page. This site is prettier and more functional to update anyway.
Syllabus If you need a quick reference or refresher, my syllabus is below. Syllabus Homework Homework in this course will be due almost every Monday at midnight. Problem sets will be posted at the link below and problems to be graded should be submitted via Gradescope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro Physics II</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/phys222/phys222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/phys222/phys222/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to Willamette&amp;rsquo;s Physics 222 course! This is my personal website, which I will update in lieu of the WISE page. This site is prettier and more functional to update anyway.
Syllabus If you need a quick reference or refresher, my syllabus is below. Syllabus Homework Homework in this course is a mix of online and video problems. Online homework will be assigned through WebWorK after each class period and will be due by the end of the next class day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mechanics</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/phys339/phys339/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/phys339/phys339/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to Willamette&amp;rsquo;s Phys 339: Mechanics course! This is my personal website and will be the primary vehicle by which I&amp;rsquo;ll pass information to you this semester. Anything posted elsewhere I&amp;rsquo;ll be very clear about!
Syllabus If you need a quick reference back to my syllabus, you can find it below: Syllabus Homework Homework in this class will be due Friday nights at midnight. We&amp;rsquo;ll be using Gradescope to submit assignments to cut back on the amount of paper I need to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astronomy</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/phys110/phys110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/phys110/phys110/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to Physics 110: Astronomy! This is my personal website, and will be the main location where I post things throughout the semester. Anything posted elsewhere will be clearly indicated and announced in class! In general this should be your one-stop-shop for everything class related.
Syllabus If you need a quick reference or review, you can find my syllabus here: Syllabus Homework We are using WebWorK this semester for homework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electromagnetism</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/phys345/phys345/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/phys345/phys345/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to Willamette&amp;rsquo;s Phys 345: Electromagnetism course! This is my personal website and will be the primary vehicle by which I&amp;rsquo;ll pass information to you this semester. Anything posted elsewhere I&amp;rsquo;ll be very clear about!
Syllabus If you need a quick reference back to my syllabus, you can find it below: Syllabus Homework Homework in this class will be due Monday nights at midnight. We&amp;rsquo;ll be using Gradescope to submit assignments to cut back on the amount of paper I need to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Physics I</title>
      <link>/website_copy/classes/phys221/phys221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 19:04:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website_copy/classes/phys221/phys221/</guid>
      <description>General Information Welcome to Willamette&amp;rsquo;s Physics 221 course! This is my personal website, which I will likely prioritize updating over the WISE pages. This site is prettier anyway&amp;hellip;
Syllabus If you need a quick reference or refresher, my syllabus is below.
&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;/website_copy/class_files/phys221/syllabus.pdf&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Syllabus &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Homework Homework in this course is a mix of written and video problems. Written homework will be assigned after each class period and will be due by the end of the next class day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
